http://www.greatmalvernpriory.org.uk/privacy435351

Great Malvern Priory | Privacy
Great Malvern Priory
Login
Username:
Password:
Privacy
HomeOnline WorshipOnline WorshipOne Service for All - 04/10One Service for All - 04/10Newsletter - 04/10Service for Sunday - 04/10Intercessions - 04/10Activities for Children & Families - 04/10September 2020September 2020One Service for All - 27/09One Service for All - 27/09Newsletter - 27/09Service for Sunday - 27/09Intercessions - 27/09Activities for Children & Families - 27/09One Service for All - 20/09One Service for All - 20/09Newsletter - 20/09Service for Sunday - 20/09Intercessions - 20/09Activities for Children & Families - 20/09One Service for All - 13/09One Service for All - 13/09Newsletter - 13/09Service for Sunday - 13/09Intercessions - 13/09Activities for Children & Families - 13/09One Service for All - 06/09One Service for All - 06/09Newsletter - 06/09Service for Sunday - 06/09Intercessions - 06/09Activities for Children & Families - 06/09August 2020August 2020One Service for All - 30/08One Service for All - 30/08Newsletter - 30/08Intercessions - 30/08One Service for All - 23/08One Service for All - 23/08Newsletter - 23/08Service for Sunday - 23/08Intercessions - 23/08One Service for All - 16/08One Service for All - 16/08Newsletter - 16/08Intercessions - 16/08One Service for All - 09/08One Service for All - 09/08Newsletter - 09/08Service for Sunday - 09/08Intercessions - 09/08One Service for All - 02/08One Service for All - 02/08Newsletter - 02/08Service for Sunday - 02/08Intercessions - 02/08July 2020July 2020One Service for All - 26/07One Service for All - 26/07Newsletter - 26/07Service for Sunday - 26/07Intercessions - 26/07Activities for Children & Families - 26/07One Service for All - 19/07One Service for All - 19/07Newsletter - 19/07Service for Sunday - 19/07Intercessions - 19/07Evensong - 19/07Activities for Children & Families - 19/07One Service for All - 12/07One Service for All - 12/07Newsletter - 12/07Service for Sunday - 12/07Intercessions - 12/07Activities for Children & Families - 12/07One Service for All - 05/07One Service for All - 05/07Newsletter - 05/07Service for Sunday - 05/07Intercessions - 05/07Evensong - 05/07Activities for Children & Families - 05/07June 2020June 2020One Service for All - 28/06One Service for All - 28/06Newsletter - 28/06Service for Sunday - 28/06Intercessions - 28/06Activities for Children & Families - 28/06One Service for All - 21/06One Service for All - 21/06Newsletter - 21/06Service for Sunday - 21/06Intercessions - 21/06Evensong - 21/06Activities for Children & Families - 21/06One Service for All - 14/06One Service for All - 14/06Newsletter - 14/06Service for Sunday - 14/06Intercessions - 14/06Activities for Children & Families - 14/06One Service for All - 07/06One Service for All - 07/06Newsletter - 07/06Service for Sunday - 07/06Intercessions - 07/06Evensong - 07/06Activities for Children & Families - 07/06May 2020May 2020One Service for All - 31/05One Service for All - 31/05Newsletter - 31/05Service for Sunday - 31/05Intercessions - 31/05Activities for Children & Families - 31/05One Service for All - 24/05One Service for All - 24/05Newsletter - 24/05Service for Sunday - 24/05Intercessions - 24/05Evensong - 24/05Activities for Children & Families - 24/05One Service for All - 17/05One Service for All - 17/05Newsletter - 17/05Service for Sunday - 17/05Intercessions - 17/05Activities for Children & Families - 17/05One Service for All - 10/05One Service for All - 10/05Newsletter - 10/05Service for Sunday - 10/05Intercessions - 10/05Evensong - 10/05Activities for Children & Families - 10/05One Service for All - 03/05One Service for All - 03/05Newsletter - 03/05Service for Sunday - 03/05Intercessions - 03/05Activities for Children & Families - 03/05April 2020April 2020One Service for All - 26/04One Service for All - 26/04Newsletter 26/04Service for Sunday - 26/04Intercessions - 26/04Evensong - 26/04One Service for All - 19/04One Service for All - 19/04Newsletter 19/04Service for Sunday - 19/04Intercessions - 19/04From the Vicar - 19/04Children's Talk - 19/04One Service for All - 12/04One Service for All - 12/04Newsletter 12/04Service for Easter SundayIntercessions - 12/04From the Vicar - 12/04Children's Talk - 12/04Good Friday - 10/04Compline for Holy WeekOne Service for All - 05/04One Service for All - 05/04Newsletter - 05/04Service for Sunday - 05/04Intercessions - 05/04From the Vicar - 05/04Children's Talk - 05/04Evensong Palm SundayMarch 2020March 2020One Service for All - 29/03One Service for All - 29/03NewsletterService for SundayFrom the VicarChildren's TalkIntercessionsThoughts from Dr Ali GrayOne Service for All - 22/03One Service for All - 22/03Mothering SundayMothering Sunday - EveningCoronavirus SermonDaily PrayerPrayer LetterVirtual Worship BandAbout UsAbout UsDonationsOur New Vicar (June 2018)MagazineFor visitors...HistoryHistoryTour the PrioryStained GlassThe Priory BellsPatronal PageThe Priory PlanElectoral RollPeopleUseful linksLegalRoute to the HIllsStonework RepairsStonework RepairsRepairs to the BuildingThe Repair ProgrammeCracks & CobwebsCarving RevealedStonework updateServicesServicesMusicMusicChoirMusic ListWorship BandOrgan RecitalsChoir CDLife EventsSermonsThe GatheringActivitiesActivitiesChildren & YouthChildren & YouthJAM ClubSNACChildren's SpaceYouth hourJunior ChoirPriory Youth GroupLifepathJunior HandbellsTerm DatesHouse GroupsMessy ChurchMissionMissionMission PartnersiAdelante! 2020Lunch BoxSocial CaringBellringingBellringingBells ProjectHand BellsPriory ShopNoticesReview of the Mystery PlayBig Quiz NightThe FriendsThe FriendsAs a Friend you will...How to join The FriendsVolunteer to helpForthcoming EventsGuided ToursPriory HistoryThe Friends' TileThe Friends & Lunch BoxRecorded TalksBook of RemembranceData ProtectionGet in touch/Amend detailsMapCalendarPhotosPhotosLight Party 2019Malvern Mystery Play 2019Lifepath 2018People and EventsViewsThe Friends' Millennium Windows
Home > Privacy
Privacy
Privacy
DATA PRIVACY NOTICE
The Parochial Church Council (PCC) of Great Malvern Priory
1. Your personal data – what is it?
Personal data relates to a living individual who can be identified from that data. Identification can be by the information alone or in conjunction with any other information in the data controller’s possession or likely to come into such possession. The processing of personal data is governed by the General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”).
2. Who are we?
The PCC and the Vicar are the two data controllers of Great Malvern Priory (contact details below). This means they decide how your personal data is processed and for what purposes.
3. How do we process your personal data?
The PCC of Great Malvern Priory complies with its obligations under the “GDPR” by keeping personal data up to date; by storing and destroying it securely; by not collecting or retaining excessive amounts of data; by protecting personal data from loss, misuse, unauthorised access and disclosure and by ensuring that appropriate technical measures are in place to protect personal data.
We use your personal data for the following purposes: -
To enable us to provide a voluntary service for the benefit of the public in a particular geographical area as specified in our constitution;
To administer membership records;
To fundraise and promote the interests of the charity;
To manage our employees and volunteers;
To maintain our own accounts and records (including the processing of gift aid applications);
To inform you of news, events, activities and services running at GMP;
To share your contact details with the Diocesan office so they can keep you informed about news in the diocese and events, activities and services that will be occurring in the diocese and in which you may be interested.
4. What is the legal basis for processing your personal data?
Explicit consent of the data subject so that we can keep you informed about news, events, activities and services and keep you informed about diocesan events.
Processing is necessary for carrying out legal obligations in relation to Gift Aid or under employment, social security or social protection law, or a collective agreement;
Processing is carried out by a not-for-profit body with a political, philosophical, religious or trade union aim provided: -
the processing relates only to members or former members (or those who have regular contact with it in connection with those purposes); and
there is no disclosure to a third party without consent.
5. Sharing your personal data
Your personal data will be treated as strictly confidential and will only be shared with other members of the church in order to carry out a service to other church members or for purposes connected with the church. We will only share your data with third parties outside of the parish with your consent.
6. How long do we keep your personal data1?
We keep data in accordance with the guidance set out in the guide “Keep or Bin: Care of Your Parish Records” which is available from the Church of England website [see footnote for link].
Specifically, we retain electoral roll data while it is still current; gift aid declarations and associated paperwork for up to 6 years after the calendar year to which they relate; and parish registers (baptisms, marriages, funerals) permanently.
7. Your rights and your personal data
Unless subject to an exemption under the GDPR, you have the following rights with respect to your personal data: -
The right to request a copy of your personal data which the PCC of Great Malvern Priory holds about you;
The right to request that the PCC of Great Malvern Priory corrects any personal data if it is found to be inaccurate or out of date;
The right to request your personal data is erased where it is no longer necessary for the PCC of Great Malvern Priory to retain such data;
The right to withdraw your consent to the processing at any time
The right to request that the data controller provide the data subject with his/her personal data and where possible, to transmit that data directly to another data controller, (known as the right to data portability), (where applicable) [Only applies where the processing is based on consent or is necessary for the performance of a contract with the data subject and in either case the data controller processes the data by automated means].
The right, where there is a dispute in relation to the accuracy or processing of your personal data, to request a restriction is placed on further processing;
The right to object to the processing of personal data, (where applicable) [Only applies where processing is based on legitimate interests (or the performance of a task in the public interest/exercise of official authority); direct marketing and processing for the purposes of scientific/historical research and statistics]
The right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioners Office.
8. Further processing
If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, not covered by this Data Protection Notice, then we will provide you with a new notice explaining this new use prior to commencing the processing and setting out the relevant purposes and processing conditions. Where and whenever necessary, we will seek your prior consent to the new processing.
9. Contact Details
To exercise all relevant rights, queries of complaints please in the first instance contact the Church Manager at Great Malvern Priory, at The Parish Office, Church Street, Great Malvern, Worcs, WR14 2AY or by email: church.manager@greatmalvernpriory.org.uk
You can contact the Information Commissioners Office on 0303 123 1113 or via email https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/email/or at the Information Commissioner's Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire. SK9 5AF.
1. Details about retention periods can currently be found in the Record Management Guides located on the Church of England website at: -https://www.churchofengland.org/more/libraries-and-archives/records-management-guides
Printable Version
Great Malvern Priory, Church Street, Malvern WR14 2AY
+44 (0) 1684 561020
This number will connect you to our answerphone
Registered Charity No. 1128064
